1.  Excuse me, are you here for the seminar?  Then please go to the second floor.
1.  請問是要參加研討會的嗎？麻煩請至二樓。  
2.  The seminar is on the second floor. Please go to the front desk to get your badges.
2.  參加研討會者，請上二樓。需要換證者，麻煩請往前方的櫃台。  
3.  If you would like to know more information about the seminar program (the time and the sessions of the seminar), you can go to the information desk at the   classroom having the seminars.
3.  如果您想要知道研討會時間及場次，您可以到該研討會的教室門口詢問服務人員。  
4.  This seminar should be paid and registered in advance. Registering on the day of the seminar is not accepted.
4.  這場研討會需要付費參加，不接受現場報名。  