1.  Excuse me, have you registered before? Please go to the entrance to line up.
1.  請問是預先登錄者嗎？麻煩請在這邊入口排隊。  
2.  Excuse me, sir. There are still people waiting in line.  Could you please go to the back of the line and wait? Thank you.
2.  先生，抱歉。後方有人在排隊等待，麻煩排隊，謝謝。  
3.  Please step forward.
3.  麻煩請往前走。  
4.  This exhibition will start from nine.
4.  提醒你，展覽要到９點才開始。  
5.  Please turn left at the entrance for the exhibition.
5.  展場入口麻煩請往左手邊進入。  
6.  We hope you will enjoy the exhibition.
6.  祝您參觀愉快。 
7.  The buyers (factory owners) are allowed to enter at 8:30 A.M.
7.  提醒你，參展廠商於８點３０才可以開始入場。  
8.  When you enter or exit the gateway, please swipe your Id card for identification.
8.  進出入口，麻煩請刷條碼，以辨識身分。  