1.  If you are interested in the booths and the map of the room, you can ask for help at the information desk.
1.  如果您要問有關於攤位位置或地圖，麻煩請到詢問台做詢問，他們會為您解答。  
2.  Please turn right when you walk out of the door, turn left at an intersection ahead, and you will see the information desk located at the very end.
2.  詢問台的位置，您可以從這個門口出去後右轉，看到路口左轉，然後走到底，就可以看到了。  
3.  There are exhibitions in Hall 1, 2 and 3.  You can go by taking our shuttle bus.  The bus stop is on the right side of the front door.
3.  一館、二館、三館都有展覽。您可以搭接駁車前往參觀，接駁車站牌在大門口右側。  
4.  Each hall provides shuttle bus every 15 minutes.
4.  每15分鐘就會有一班接駁車，它都會在每一館停靠。  
5.  The restaurant is on the second floor, and the convenience store in on the third floor.
5.  餐廳在2樓，便利商店在3樓。  
6.  You can take this escalator to the second floor and then go straight ahead, take a left down the hallway and you will see another escalator which will take 6.  you down to the first floor.  You will see the counter behind you after a couple steps.
6.  可從這個手扶梯上2樓，直走走到底再左轉，就可以看到另外一個手扶梯下1樓，然後往後方走就可以看到你要找的櫃檯了。  
7.  If you want to take the shuttle bus to The World Trade Center in Hall 1, please go to the right-hand side of the entrance door.
7.  要往世貿一館的接駁車，請於大門出口右手方，即可到達。  
8.  If you want to go to the nurse's office, please go to the first floor.  It’s at the end of area K
8.  您要到醫護室，請往一樓Ｋ區到底。.
9.  Escalators are situated on both the left and right side of the exhibition.  You can visit the exhibition on the first floor and forth floor, thanks.
9.  展場內部左右分別都有手扶梯，可參觀１樓及４樓的展覽。  
10.  Please go straight ahead and you will see the lavatory.
10.  廁所直走到底就可以看到了，謝謝！  
11.  If you want to reach the taxi pick-up point, then please take the escalator to B1 floor.
11.  計程車乘車處，麻煩請搭手扶梯至Ｂ１。
