1.  Excuse me, which exhibition would you like to visit?
1.  請問您要參觀哪個展覽？  
2.  Are you going to the Food Exhibition? Please go to the left counter and for your badge. For the Car Exhibition, please go to the right counter for your badges.
2.  請問是要參觀食品展的嗎？麻煩到左邊櫃檯換證。如果是要參觀車展，請至右邊櫃檯做換證。
3.  Sorry, this exhibition is only open to businesses of related industries.
3.  本次展覽只提供給相關業者入場。抱歉，它不對外開放。  
4.  The exhibition starts from 10:00 A.M. to 5:30 P.M from the first to the third day. The last day will end at 3:00 P.M.
4.  展覽第一天至第三天的時間為上午10點至下午5點30分。最後一天結束的時間為下午3點。  
5.  This special gift is only provided for visitors who made an appointment in advance.
5.  小禮物只提供給預先訪客領取。  
6.  Because of the limited amount of bags, we provide these bags to the first hundred visitors every day.
6.  因為手提袋數量有限，每日提供前１００名的訪客。  
7.  Excuse me, I do not quite understand your handwriting, would you please write it again or spell the words for me, thanks.
7.  抱歉，您的手寫資料我看不太懂，能不能重寫或者這幾個字拼給我聽，謝謝！！  
8.  This is a questionnaire, please help me fill it in.
8.  這邊有一份問卷，麻煩請幫我做填寫。  